Downloaded @ subs4free.club
- So, today, I give
you a sneak peak
where my nuptials will
take place.
Oh my goodness.
For those who've been
following my wedding story,
you know I met my man,
Malcolm Wright, last year
and he wooed me with wine,
trips and this rock!
I'm so lucky.
I always wanted a
guy like Malcolm.
I wish my Dad would have
been here to meet him.
I know he would loved Malcolm
because Malcolm
is a good provider
and that was
important to my Dad.
As a matter of fact,
my Dad used to
work security here
and he always talked about
how beautiful the weddings were.
I hate my Daddy
can't walk me down the aisle,
but I know he'll be
watching me from Heaven.
OK, are you guys
ready to do this?
Let's do this.
Isn't it beautiful in here?!
# 8daysleft, #MrandMrs,
#LoveMeSomeHim,
#HappilyEverAfter.
- Ms. Logan, welcome back!
We're getting close to the date.
- Yes, I know, eight
days to be exact.
- Have all 200 guests confirmed?
- Absolutely.
Malcolm's family owns
the most prestigious
black law firm in DC.
I have people that
I don't even know
DMing me to attend!
- I bet!
- My final payment.
- Congratulations!
You will be saying, "I
do," in one of the most
beautiful venues in the city.
- It's happening!
- Tia, how are you this morning?
- I'm wonderful, Bruce.
It is a beautiful Fridaymorning
and love is in the air.
- There's not much love
out there on inbound 295.
Traffic is really slow
because everybody's merging
into one lane because of
all the work that's going on.
- Hmm, if you're heading
in that direction,
allow for additional driving
time for your morning commute.
Here's Michelle for more
traffic details.
Too many times, hey Tracy!
- Good morning!
TJ set up a morning meeting.
- Oh girl, you look good!
- So do you!
- Surprise!
- Oh my goodness.
- To the bride to be,
this is just a little something
from all of us at WBX.
Congratulations, girl!
- Awe, ya know what,
truthfully, I have you to thank!
Had you not let me do
that interview with Malcolm,
I might've ended up a
miserable, lonely soul.
Shelby, join the party!
- Oh, how sweet.
Too bad, I actually
have work to do.
- Well, from all of us,
we still say congratulations
and we just hope and pray
you have a beautiful union.
Congratulations again, girl.
- And girl, thanks for
giving us all hope.
- Oh, see that?
Mm, excuse me ladies.
My man is calling.
Hey babe!
- Babe, I need you.
- Awe, I need you too.
- No, no, I need
you here for brunch.
- Right now?
- I'm meeting with Fred
Strota and his wife.
I just need you here
to entertain her
while I close this deal.
It could be a big client for us.
- Well babe,
I'm kind of in the middle of this party.
- Babe, I know, I don't
wanna pull you away, OK,
but he owns over 50 stores
and airports across the country.
He's old school.
They've been
married for 40 years
and his wife, Sarina,
is a fan of yours, so please,
I know if you're here,
this deal is done.
- Well, I am off air
and it is Friday.
I guess I can come.
- You are my lifesaver.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- I'll text you the address.
- Your fiance is
really determined.
I've never seen anyone go
after my husband's business
with such tenacity.
- Yes, he's very persistent.
- Well, when I see something I want,
I go after it, ma'am.
- I imagine that's
how he snagged you.
- Yes ma'am, it is.
- You two remind me of us.
- Ah, if we could
only be so lucky.
- Can I get you
something to drink?
- Yes, I'd like to have
a glass of Pinot Grigio.
- Oh, you need to
try their cabernet.
- I don't really want red, babe.
- You'll love it.
Bring her a glass of
the Opus One Cabernet.
Trust me.
So, Mr. Strota,
I know that you're close to acquiring
50 fast food chains and
we've done seven similar deals
in the last four years.
Four more than any other
firm you're considering.
- You have all the right things to say,
don't you?
- Especially when it comes
to securing what I deserve.
Bottom line, we're the
best team for the job.
- You know,
this was supposed to be an informal brunch,
which is why I brought
Sarina along to begin with.
- Don't believe that.
He can't make any
decisions without me.
- She is right about that.
But I can say that,
I am very impressed.
I will be speaking
with my partner
about having Wright,
Moore, and Wright
handling our legal
affairs going forward.
- Sounds good.
Well?
I told you.
Perfection.
- Jillian look, TJ
threw me a bridal shower
at the office, look!
- Oh, so kind.
- Look, look, look!
It's so nice. - Wait, wait.
What is this face, Tia?
- Shelby happened.
- I'm gon' have
to make a meme of this.
This is the face you
make when a guy tell you,
"I got that good
Polish sausage,"
but he show up with
a vienna sausage.
- The disappointment.
- Excuse me,
can you tell me where I could find...
- Oh I'm sorry, I
don't work here.
I don't work here.
- Okay.
- Why the heck,
why they keep thinkin' I work here?
Do I look like a
librarian or something?
- Well, you are shuffling
aroundyour client's books again.
So disruptive!
- I am a publicist.
Prominent bookshelf
space is everything.
You know that.
- When are you going to start
your own publishing company?
- Uh, whenever you
have a bestseller.
I mean, how great would
it be to have your book
splashed on every bookshelf,
The Joy Of Having It All
by my girl, Tia Logan.
- I can't wait!
- Uh, neither can the publisher.
So, what's taking you so
long with the next draft?
- Between planning the wedding
and Malcolm's social
calendar, I'm busy!
- Oh, you're stepping
into your role as a Steffard.
I mean, trophy wife.
- My man sees me as his equal.
- Sure, he does.
So what's up with the wedding?
- Well, I have my
dress fitting tomorrow
and I made my final payment
on the venue yesterday,
so nothing.
Don't start, Jillian. - What?!
- Don't!
- I didn't say nothin'!
- Yes, I, don't start Jillian.
Non-verbal, stop it.
I already told you,
Malcolm is buying us a vacation property
and paying for the honeymoon.
I wanna contribute.
Who wants to be one of those
women who has to depend
on their man for everything?
- Not everything,
just this expensive ass wedding.
You shouldn't have to
be paying for nothing.
- Whatever Jillie, let's go.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- After I get this book.
- Really?
- What?
You just said who wants
to be one of those women
who have to rely on
her man for everything.
I don't need him if I got these.
I know 'cause I'm a
strong black woman.
- Yeah, strong, real strong.
Wow, this is nice
and unexpected.
- Just a little something
special to say thank you.
I couldn't have pulled
off brunch without you.
- Awe babe, you
did all the work.
I just say there
and looked fabulous.
- Well you must've
did something right
'cause right after you left,
she asked me for your email.
Said she wants to invite
you to speak at some
Essence Women's
Business Luncheon.
- Really?
- Babe,
how many times do I have to tell you?
We make a great team.
Mr. Stroto called this
afternoon and they want us
to start negotiations.
- I am so proud of you, baby.
- For us.
- Mmm, babe,
these strawberries are delicious.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I hand dipped them
myself just for you.
Oh, there's one more thing.
I'll be right back.
- He didn't hand dip nothin'.
He bought...
- Close your eyes and
hold out your hands.
Open em.
- Oh.
- Something blue.
It was my grandmother's and now,
she wants you to have it.
- Oh baby, it's so beautiful.
Oh,
I am the luckiest woman in the whole world.
- Yeah, I can't argue with that.
- Excuse me, do you
have any crackers?
The bride wouldn't let
us eat before the fitting
and I'm starving!
- The bride can't be bloated!
- Oh, you look stunning!
The queen approves.
Listen, did Malcolm ever
tell you where you're going
for the honeymoon?
- Nope.
- Child, I don't
know how you do it.
I got to know where
I'm going in advance.
I just can't be going no
anywhere with anybody.
- It's called trust,
control freak.
It's OK to let the man lead.
Sometimes, I like to follow.
- Excuse me, ma'am,
can you untighten that?
That shit is way too tight.
She's losing her mind,
she's just saying anything.
Going no anywhere.
Tia, you look so beautiful.
- What?
Tia!
What Tia?
What Tia?!
- Malcolm!
What are you doin' with her?
- Tia, wait, wait, wait, baby.
- What are you doin' with her?
- OK!
- She's your ex!
- Baby, calm down.
Stop recording!
- I trusted you!
The wedding is off!
- What do you mean?
- Malcolm, you need
to handle all this.
- Look, this...
- Bitch, what?
Move, Malcolm.
- Wait, Tia baby, chill, chill.
- Cocky, no one
fault son of a bitch!
How could he do this to me?
- Well, I hate to
tell ya baby but,
a man who lies about
dipping his strawberries
will lie about where
he's dipping his banana
with his dumb ass.
Oh, you might wanna see this.
- What, my bleak future?
- Uh, something like that.
- God.
Oh my God.
It's everywhere.
- In today's evening news...
- YouTube, the Gossip Room?
Today's popular stories?!
- And...
- We're seeing her like
we've never seen her before.
- This is not what
you think it is!
- The wedding is off!
The wedding is off!
- Baby wait.
- Malcolm, you need to
handle all this. - Shut up.
Bitch, what?!
- Can you say #AngryBlackWoman?
- Oh my God.
- We need to go
over these policies
just to make sure that
our client isn't at fault.
Malcolm.
Malcolm!
Policies, client.
- I know, I know.
I'm sorry you had to come
over here tonight, Rayna.
I can't go back into
the office tomorrow.
I mean, my phone is
already blowin' up.
- There have been some
text messages about you.
- What are they saying?
Nevermind.
- Why do men propose if
they're not even ready?
- Wait, wait, wait.
Didn't you say you
were just in the office
talkin' 'bout how you
were breakin' up with David
'cause he hadn't proposed yet?
- That's different.
- No, no, no, no, exactly.
Damned if you do,
damned if you don't.
Let's just get back to work.
- I was grabbing the
mail earlier like you asked
and I found this in the uh...
- How many of those
have you eaten?
Really, Tia?
- Everyone's laughing at me.
- Look, pull yourself
together, friend!
You know, I'm startin'
to worry about you.
You lookin' all sloppy!
You gotta go back
to work glowin'.
I don't want you
lookin' like this!
- Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have to call out,
I can't go in there.
- Why not?!
You dumped him and then
you whooped his ass
with a bouquet of calla lilies.
In this case scenario,
you the badass.
- If anything,
they laughing at him, not you!
- Are you sure?
- You damn right I'm sure.
Now get your cake
pop, fire startin' ass
off my couch, take a shower,
and then march back
to work tomorrow like
gettin' rid of Malcolm
was the best thing that
ever happened to you.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you right.
- Damn right, I'm right.
Yeah, I'm right.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Oh, yeah, yeah,
get it together!
You got this, girl!
You good!
You beautiful!
This shit ain't gonna end well.
- I'm going to strangle
hislying ass and kick him in the...
Can everyone clear
the room please?
We need to talk.
- WBX employees shall
not commit any act
or do anything which might
tend to bring the employee
into public disrepute,
contempt, scandal,
or ridicule,
or which might tend to reflect unfavorably
on the network.
Any sponsor of
the program or any
sub-sponsors advertising agency.
- So can they suspend me?
- I'm no lawyer,
but I would say yes.
- I gave up my place
when I got engaged.
Now because of Malcolm,
I'm losing my home,
my dignity and my job.
- You can get another job.
You can get another apartment.
Dignity, child, it's overrated.
Good thing you left
Malcolm before the wedding!
- Just...
I don't know,
I just thought everything was perfect!
I feel so stupid!
I feel... - Don't, don't!
You're good!
It's not as bad as it seem!
Look, the internet will
soon forget about you.
Your heart will heal
soon, I promise!
I'll start canceling some
of the wedding stuff.
- The venue.
- You will absolutely
love this venue.
Take a look at our
pamphlet and if you have
any questions, let me know.
My name is Katie.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
Ms. Logan, what brings you by?
- The wedding is off.
- Oh, let's just say postponed.
We don't like the word off.
What happened?
This is you?
I am so sorry.
You OK?
- I will be once
I get my refund.
- Man, you really
let him have it.
- Excuse me, Katie.
Katie, dear!
I need my refund.
- Oh, we don't like
the word refund.
- Well then, what
word would you like?
I need my money?
Please.
- OK, don't go all
angry black woman,
angry African Amer...
Angry woman of col...
Don't be upset.
Let's just push
the date back a bit
just in case things change.
But then your date will
have to be within the next
12 months or your payment
in full will be forfeited.
- Are you saying I
can't get my money back?
- Cancellations and refundsmust
be made 30 days in advance.
It's in your contract.
I am sorry.
- That's $50,000, Katie.
Gone.
- We don't like the word gone.
Let's just say it was an
expensive lesson in love.
Yeah!
- Oh shit.
God.
What's up, world?
I know I haven't done a follow
up video to my wedding story
since well, you know.
My last post was four
days ago right here in this
very spot and I was full of joy,
walking on clouds.
Now today, I stand
in the same spot
but now the clouds are
gone and so is my refund.
Same spot, different place.
#Isntltlronic,
#LoveDontLiveHere,
#WheresMyRefund,
#AngrilyEverAfter.
Damn that was a bad,
that was a bad idea.
Hmm.
So, guess what
happened today, guys.
My book got shelved
indefinitely.
Their reason, my book
title no longer works.
I mean, think about it.
How can I talk about the
joys of having it all
when I have nothing.
Hey!
Oh my gosh,
there are way more of you following me
than when I was talking
about my wedding stories.
Shut it, I heard that.
No, PreacherMan32, I
do not need prayer.
No, you can not
lay hand, can you...
Nobody was talkin' to you.
Do you always open
your mouth this wide?
Is it me or does
misery love company?
I said shut it!
- Have you gone
to counseling together?
It's been three weeks.
Tia, how many times have
I told you, you do not
throw the baby out
with the bath water.
Tia, how come I don't
see your face anymore?
Where are you?
- I'm here, I'm here
Mom, I'm here, I'm here.
- There you go, OK.
- I'm here.
- I'm talking to you.
Now, I am very sorry.
P.S. I talked to him
and I believe him.
He apologized.
Now your Dad, he
worked two jobs Tia,
for you to have a
really good life
and he only wanted you to
be able to have some stability
and have a good man
take care of you
and Malcolm is that.
- Mom, I do not need a
man to take care of me.
- Yes, you do.
- Mom, I will get another job.
Mom, no!
Dad taught me that too, ya know?
I don't need a man
to take care of me.
- You're getting older.
How are you gonna have kids?
What man is gonna want
you if you keep getting older?
Malcolm is there,
he's ready for you.
So be with him.
Are you tryin' to kill me?
- Mom, calm down.
Is it past your zanny time?
- I don't know, I
might need a zanny.
You know what, I do.
I'm gonna come over there.
- No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, I love you Mom.
I gotta call you back.
I thought I told you to
throw that stuff away!
- Girl, what is this,
silk chiffon, this feels so good
and no ya didn't.
You said you didn't want it.
It's a difference.
Now,
if Malcolm is foolish enough to buy it,
I'm smart enough to wear it.
And I heard what your Mama said.
- I just need to find
another really good job,
something she can celebrate
so she can tell her friends
about it and she'll
get off my back.
Problem is, no one will hire me.
- You just need to apply
forjobs that don't have the titles
news anchor or reporter in it.
- But that's what I do, Jillie.
- Baby, you have a whole
Masters in Journalism.
You could do whatever you want!
Mm,
that's probably a matching bracelet for my,
our earrings.
Uh, hello.
You're not the delivery boy.
- No, uh, I'm Van Joyner.
Is Tia Logan in?
We went to grad school
togetherand I wanna talk to her
about an opportunity.
- Oh come in, come on in.
Tia, it's a man here.
- There she is, look at that.
In the flesh, huh?
How you doin' darlin'?
- Oh my gosh!
Hey! - It's been a long time.
- I haven't seen you
since Northwestern!
Sit down, what are you...
- Yeah, yeah.
- What are you doin' here?
- Well, it's funny that you ask.
I actually work
in television now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
My colleague mentioned
that you applied for
a news reporter job
with our sister station.
Your address is on your resume.
- Oh.
- I want you to come
on as one of the hosts
for The Gossip Room.
- Yes, yes, say yes!
- I mean,
I hope you were excited as your friend is.
Have you see the show?
- Yeah, I think
like once or twice.
It's two kids
sittin' around a desk
just talking.
- Yeah, they're adults,
not kids, yeah.
- Yeah well, they act like kids.
- Actually,
it's a daily half hour news entertainment
program averaging 3.2
million viewers weekly.
The show is ranked number
four in adults 18 through 34.
We rank number two in
women 18 through 34.
We're syndicated in New
York, Phoenix, Austin,
and seven other cities.
- Well, what's your affiliation?
- I'm the Executive Producer.
- What?!
Oh my God, Van?!
I'm impressed!
- Hey, I'm the one
that's impressed.
I've been following your career.
Always knew you'd do
some great things.
- Van Joyner, this is
a really nice surprise.
- Yeah, same here.
Our goal here is not always
to shock and entertain.
We also like to educate.
- Who are you educating
when you poke fun
at overweight celebrities
and expose affairs?
- Look,
I don't always agree
with everything you do,
but my first goal is to
keep the show on the air.
My second goal is to expand
into other shows on the air.
Let me show you to your office.
Right here.
Well, I'm gonna let
you get settled in.
I hope you're ready.
We're gonna go live
tomorrow morning.
- But I don't have any
emails to give any advice on.
- A few ladies emailed in
once the post went viral.
We'll use one of those.
Soon as the show airs,
it'll start pouring in.
- Thank you again
for this opportunity.
- Don't mention it.
I'm gonna have some
guys come in here
and straighten things
up for you, OK?
- OK.
- Let me know if
you need anything.
- I will, thank you Van.
- Yeah, no problem.
- Oh yo, slow down.
What's goin' on, how you been?
Bring it in.
- Hi, I'm Tia.
- OK cool, we know who you are.
We all know who you are.
You still angry?
- No, I'm fine, and you are?
- I'm Austin B.
- Oh yeah, you look familiar.
- Yeah, I'm the host.
Now, Brianna's the
co-host and sister,
you are the co-co-host.
- OK, do you have a
specialty or a segment?
- Yeah of course.
I do all the music, the beeps,
all the albums and
everything like that.
Ain't nobody smashing
this industry
unless I know about it first.
- OK, it was nice
to meet you Austin.
- Yeah of course but
hang on a second now.
Van got you doin' the
girl's advice, correct?
- Yes.
- Try not to make
us men look bad.
- It's not my intent.
- OK, but I'm just sayin',
you sisters always got
something negative to
say about us brothers.
- It's only when you deserve it.
- Why don't you just report
on one good brother a week,
just one, but it gives sisters
hope and it lets em know
there's still brothers likewalking
around every single day.
- OK Austin,
I'm just getting my ideas together
but I promise you I'll
keep that in mind.
See ya later.
- Of course, all right, Tia?
See you on set!
- Oh, hello, hello,
hello, hello.
- Damn, what took you so long?
- Errr, 'scuse me, hi.
I'm Brianna.
I didn't get to
meet you yesterday.
- Tia!
- All right come
on, get focused.
We're about to go
live, let's go.
- Can we get some
more light in here?
- In five, four, three,
two... - Your mama.
Yo, what's goin' on?
Welcome to The Gossip Room.
Now,
a lot of crazy things took place yesterday.
A lot went down but
don't even trip.
You know we got you.
Before we get started,
we have a new addition to
The Gossip Room, Ms. Tia Logan.
- Thank you, Austin.
Brianna, I'm so happy
to be here with you.
We're live, America!
- Yeah uh, you
might've recognized her
for the crazy viral video
a couple weeks ago.
- Or you may have known
her from the morning news.
Either way, she
hangin' with us now.
- She one of the
best in the business.
- Yeah!
- Tia,
let's not work those spec because I know
it's about to be lit, lit.
- All right Rihanna.
This segment of the show iscalled
Ask The #AngryBlackWoman.
Oh.
- Hey, hey, get it, get it.
- Um...
Uh OK um, today's
letter comes from Paula
and boy, it's a doozy.
Paula and her man ended things and now,
she's suing him
for back pay of labor.
- Back pay for sex?
- No, for cooking and cleaning.
- Hell yeah, that's
what I'm talkin' about.
- Well,
my advice would be to really
think about this lawsuit, Paula.
What if he comes back
and sues you for his labor?
Maybe he washed your
car, cut your grass.
This could go back and
forth in court until you owe
thousands of dollars
in court fees.
I say cut your losses and
give Darnell his dog back.
- She took his dog?
- Yes,
a K-9 was apprehended but I assure you
that no animals were harmed.
I'm Tia Logan and
that's my time.
- Man, hell no!
- She's just warming up.
- No, it is called
Angry Black Woman.
Not stick up my ass woman.
Come on, man!
- And now you being
so angry, right?
I ain't yellin' in the hall.
Brother, it's all good.
She'll get into it.
She'll get into
it, I promise you.
- All right man.
- I need you, Austin.
You're my go to
brother, my A1 baby.
- I'm A1.
- Yeah, you the A1.
You know dat.
- Yeah!
- OK.
- Loosen up a bit.
Yeah you know, like
on set, we flow,
ya know like a rap side for Lennon,
flow you know?
What is that, a boat neck?
Girl, you gotta let the cleavage,
you gotta let the
girls show a little bit.
Let em loose, let em hurt below.
- Can I talk to
you for a minute?
- Yeah, I'm gon'
talk to you tomorrow.
Remember what I said.
Let it flow, let it flow.
- Thank you.
- OK, y'all gettin' acquainted.
- Yeah, it was a
disaster, I know.
- Not quite a tsunami but
a 2.1 on the Richter scale.
- Tomorrow, I'm
on it, I promise.
It's a new format for me.
- Just be yourself!
Let your natural charm and
professionalism shine through!
You good.
- Got it, you right.
Malcolm, what are
you doing here?
- Came to take you
to lunch or dinner.
- I'm busy.
- Van Joyner.
- Malcolm Wright.
- How did you even
know I was here?
- I saw it online.
Very impressive presence.
- Oh thanks, thanks yeah.
I'm gonna give you
two a minute, yeah.
- Oh, tomorrow, expect
a whole new Tia.
- I ain't even worried
about it, aight?
Aight brother.
- You look incredible.
- I only agreed to go to
dinner with you to get you
out of my office.
- I just wanted to have
a nice sit down dinner
so we could talk.
- I'm not falling
for your tricks.
You cheated, there's
nothing to talk about.
- Cheated is a
stretch, all right?
We kicked it, sure, but
I don't want Cammie.
You are my future.
I just, I got scared.
I thought that I could
have my last little bit of fun
before I made my commitment.
- The ring was your commitment.
- I was wrong Tia, damn!
I'm sorry!
Do you know how much
money I've been puttin' out
trying to apologize?
What more do you want from me?
- I just want you to stop!
I don't trust you, period.
And I know you didn't dip
them damn strawberries.
- Really?
Tia!
- You just gon' have
your feet on the table
like you at home?
OK girl,
you look like you bout to bring it today!
- Oh yeah girl, I'm ready.
- Yes, OK!
Your cute self.
- You ain't ready,
you ain't ready.
- All right man,
let's go ahead and hop into this first
segment of the day,
Angry Black Woman.
Go ahead, Tia.
- All right yes, so today,
I have a letter from Tahina.
She caught her boyfriend
going behind her back
trying to sabotage a
potential job because he didn't
want her salary to
be higher than his.
She wants to know should
she break up with him over this.
- That's a good one.
- Well I'll tell you what this
angry black woman thinks.
He's insecure and if you
think it's going to stop there,
you're wrong!
Sis, he's always going
to be competing with you
and this is never going
to work in a marriage.
So if you wanna be
his girlfriend forever
and allow him to
dictate your ceiling,
then yeah, stay!
But if you want a real
relationship with someone who
wants you to be your best self,
he gots to go!
That's what I say.
That's all I'm saying.
Shouldn't it be out?
- Come on, bad self!
- First of all,
her name is Kahina.
So her best self
is off the table.
- You know what, see there?
That's why you need to know your history,
young man.
Let me school you
right quick, OK?
See, Al Kahina was a
powerful African warrior
who took command of a army
so that the Arabs wouldn't be
invading the land.
To stop from losing,
she burned the land down
instead of seeing it taken
over by non-African, what?!
- Aha, boom!
- You saw that knowledge
hit him in the face like that?
Real slick like?
- You didn't know that.
You didn't know that,
Brianna, sit back.
Shut up, this eh eh.
- You know what?
There are a lot of brothers
out there who are too insecure
or too white washed to
handle a woman with a
strong African name.
Maybe our friend Austin
here prefers names like
Becky or Sissy.
You know what it is.
You guys, leave me
a comment about that
and I'll get at you tomorrow.
Power to the people! - Woo!
- Justin, Shannon!
Don't touch me.
- Yes, girl!
- Hey guys, it's your
angry black woman here.
Make sure you keep those
emailscoming and tune in tomorrow.
We're going to be talking
about jealous roommates.
#SingleBlackFemale.
- You up late.
- You goin' out with Rick?
- Butch.
- I don't know how you do it.
I can't date more than
one man at a time without
getting caught up.
- That's 'cause you kiss.
In my world and in my rule book,
you never, ever, ever kiss.
When I kiss,
I'm ready to take it to the next level.
- You're still doing that?
- That is what keep
em coming back, OK?
Don't wait up, good night!
Maybe I'll ask Butch
if he got a little brother.
- What's up brothers?
Guess what.
You've got your first gig.
Austin and Brianna are
often paid to host parties.
You've been asked to host
MySister's Keeper rooftop brunch.
- Oh, that's great!
- You might wanna think
about getting yourself posters
and negotiating the fees
'cause you bout to
be busy, all right?
- Awesome!
- Nice flowers.
- Hello ladies!
Are you ready to excel?!
- Hello Malcolm.
- We got one hour.
Frisco is in town this weekend
and he wants to see me.
- One hour, got it.
- Now if you went on
Tinder like I told you,
you would've had a date.
- Just hush and hold my arm!
Oh and if anyone asks,
you're my person.
- Isn't that your co-host?
- Yep.
- Mm, he is a lot
cuter in person.
- What?
- Yes, look at him.
Look at him standing on
his little tippy toes.
You think he like older women?
- Jillie.
I thought higher of you.
- What?!
Look at his face, I
will sit all on that.
I'm just sayin'.
- Hello.
- Van, hi!
This is such a fancy party.
You know Jillie.
- Oh yes, hi.
- How are you?
- Good, good, thank you.
Ross Chow Media is our
primary stakeholder.
See there Ross Chow, the owner?
He loves a good party.
- Oh, she used to own the
PR company that I work for.
Sienna is a powerhouse.
- Wait, I didn't know
you worked in PR.
- Yeah.
- She's my publicist.
- Oh, let me know if
you need my services.
- Hey, say no more darlin'.
- I got you.
- Knew I liked her,
I knew I liked her.
All right you ladies have fun.
I'm gonna go ahead and
mingle a little bit, OK?
All right, good seeing you.
- You too.
- I see you lookin' at him.
- What? No.
- Let me see your eyes.
You was lookin' at him.
Come on, let's go.
We can go get his number.
Talk to him.
- Don't do that, behave.
- Shut up.
- How y'all doin'?
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you, thank you.
Tonight we are
celebrating five years.
It's been an amazing ride but
we've just scratched
the surface.
I wanna thank our producers,
our executives,
and of course,
our sponsors because without you,
we wouldn't even have a show.
Last but not least, my
three amazing hosts.
Austin Bean.
Brianna Williams!
And our latest
addition, Tia Logan.
Without you guys,
we definitelywould not have a show.
Now, I must say,
our newest segment has really taken off.
Our subscriber base has
reached one million.
Tia Logan, please say
something to the people.
- That's my best friend!
- I just wanna
say I am so grateful
for this new journey and
I'm so happy that I get a
open, honest platform to
talk about love issues
and raw emotions.
Thank you Van,
thank you Gossip Room for trusting me.
I really look forward
to contributing to
the show's future success.
Thank you guys so much.
- Thank you baby.
You look beautiful, by the way.
On that note,
toast, cheers y'all!
- Tia.
- Corley!
- I thought I'd find you here.
- Wow!
- I'm sure it's good
to know that you're the
smartest flea in the sand box.
- You are not about
to do CC like that.
How dare you say Ciara
can't hold her own tour!
- First of all, I love CC
with her fine ass.
I'm just sayin' she can't
run a tour by herself!
- OK, now ya trippin'!
Tell him, Tia.
- Yeah, I met Ciara
once at a party.
Sweet girl, tall too.
- Cut for commercial.
- Hey, you OK?
You seem like
you're a little off.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- OK.
- Brianna, come here.
Where did you study journalism?
I'm just curious.
- Oh, I didn't.
I got this job right after I
reached two million followers.
- I like Van.
What should I do?
- I don't know.
You two go way back.
Date him.
- I mean, it could get
awkward if he doesn't
feel the same way.
Plus I'm pretty sure it's
against my work policy,
so if I wanna keep my job,
dating Van isn't an option.
- All right, fine.
Date him then.
- Oh, eww.
Yeah, I'm sorry
teddy, ya touched it.
Ugh,
why do you have that in your guest bedroom?
- Ya never know when ya
need a little hot dog in your bun.
Go on a dating app!
You won't talk to Van and
you better not talk to Malcolm.
- Oh my God, you
talk to Malcolm?
- It was only like twice.
- Give me your phone.
I'm signing you up
on a dating app.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Yes, I don't
care what you say.
- Not a dating app.
- Well, use this then.
That's your best bet.
- It's on me!
Hmm.
Hmm!
- Trying to make you laugh.
- I think I want dessert, you?
- Now that you ask.
Meet my wife, Crystal.
We would love to
have you for dessert.
- Ah hell nah!
You that angry back
chick that's messin' it up
for all the players over here?
I'm out, swipe left.
- You great.
- I cannot remember the
last time I laughed so hard.
Thank you for
tonight, thank you.
- Oh no, thank you.
I had fun, thank you.
- Yeah, oh you know what,
sincewe both like horror movies,
we should go see that new movie.
What's that movies, it's um,
put out the um,
is everything OK?
- Yeah, yeah, just tallying.
Your portion of the bill
comes out to $49.87.
I put the appetizer on
your bill since you ate
three-fourths of it,
but I'll happily put
one-fourth on mine.
- Hi Malcolm.
- You picked up.
How are you?
- I'm fine, just
thinkin' about my Dad.
How are you?
- Good.
I wanna see you.
Tia.
- I don't know, Malcolm.
- Please just come
over tomorrow night.
How much pain are you
gonna put me through?
Please baby.
Hey.
Why didn't you use your key?
- It's in the box of your
stuff that I set on fire.
Why are you playing
Kenny Lattimore.
You know I love some Kenny.
- Come here.
- You know, I'm a
big fan of your work.
I saw you.
- Oh yeah, I'm a big
fan of your hair cut
lookin' like a geisha.
- A what?
- I need a massage.
- What in the hell?
Jillian!
- Hey there, superstar!
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, Van wanted me to do
some PR work for the show.
- So I'm just here you know,
doing old promos with her.
- What is that?
- It's nothing, go ahead.
- It don't look like nothin'.
- Is that the ring...
You saw him?
- It's just a piece ofjewelry,
Jillian, it's nothing.
- No, that's something!
- You saw Malcolm.
- It's just a piece of
jewelry, it's nothing.
- Really Tia?
We had this
conversation already.
I can't believe you!
- Get in my office.
- The whole conversation
and you just disregarded
everything y'all
talked, all right.
I don't gotta know.
- Really Tia?
I can't believe you
let that snake back in!
- He's not back in.
- Really?
'Cause you got Malcolm
written all over your body.
- Where?
- A1 sauce.
See, you gotta watch
your surroundings.
- You're right, what's up boss?
What's goin' on?
- Is Jillian still here?
- I was feeling
bad and I got weak.
- Yeah, she actually
goin' out on Tia
right now about a ring.
- Jillian, the dating
thing isn't working.
He called, so I went to see him.
- And?
- About a ring?
- Yeah, I mean,
I guess she went to go talk to her ex.
She got a ring on her finger.
She might be engaged,
I'm tryin' to figure it out
right now actually.
- Well have Jillian see
me before she leaves, OK?
- Yeah, you know I
got anything for you.
- This is why I hired
you for The Gossip Room.
- I'm gon' go gossip.
- Yeah, go gossip.
- All right, boss.
- In your office.
- Yeah, in my office.
- What's important is that
it's not happening again.
Never, ever.
This is the last time.
I hate sneaking
around during lunch.
- Well stop sneaking
and move back in.
- Mr. Grayson, I'm
so sorry I'm late.
My last meeting was good, bad.
It ran over, I'm here.
- All right.
We had said some
publishers are very excited
to work with you still.
So tell me your idea.
- OK, I wanna take the
stories of the women
who have been reaching out to me
and make a compilation
of real stories.
- And the stories
are compelling.
Some are even scandalous.
- And you have the
rights to these stories?
- I will get them.
I just wanted to
test your interest.
- I'll read a few,
see if you got something there.
Eh, I will be in touch.
- Hey, that's a good start.
Real good start.
- Your lips.
- All right world,
how are you doing?
Today's letter is from Mia.
Mia has strong feelings
for a really good friend
but she's afraid that if shetells
him how she really feels,
it might affect what they have.
- No, don't do that.
Let it happen naturally,
do not put yourself out there.
Once you do that,
you can't go back!
And yo, once they
break up with you,
they gon' act like oh,
they had the upper hand
the whole entire time
and that's not the case.
Damn that.
- You good, bro?
You the angry black woman now?
- Oh no, I'm good!
I'm just sayin', you
know what I'm sayin'.
I'm just tryin' to help.
- OK.
- I saw be honest.
Test the waters.
Give him signals to let
him know you're interested
and see how he responds.
If you get nothing, back up.
But make sure he's single.
Don't be that chick.
- I wanna check in with you.
I know it's been a
couple of months.
You still happy?
- Yeah, I think I'm adjusted.
- OK, you got a lot of fans.
- Oh, I have a lot of
enemies too, trust me.
This one lady asked me
for Malcolm's number
because she said I obviously
don't know how to keep a man.
- Wait, so you two
aren't back together?
- Nope!
- Can I get anything
to drink for you two?
- Yes, I will have a Hudson neat
and the lady will have...
You not gon' drink?
- Oh, I thought you
were gonna order for me.
- I mean, I can make
a suggestion but,
you know your palette
better than I do.
- Well, in that case,
the lady will have
a glass of pinot grigio.
So, I don't want
this to get awkward
because I know
you're my boss but,
I feel like there's something
happening between us.
- Tia.
- Shelby!
- Hi!
And uh, who might this be?
- This is my boss, Van Joyner.
This is Shelby,
my old co-worker.
- Yes, Ivander Joyner right?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Yes, I think we
interviewed you once
when you first launched
your gossip show.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
You know, for a second,
Ithought I interrupted something.
- Nope, nothing!
Nothing at all.
- Oh, you know,
someone said you were working over there.
- You know, we should
have someone set it up
so Tia comes on
the morning show.
I mean, since coming on ourshow,
our numbers have increased
and you know, she speaks
at events all over DC.
- Great idea!
I'll have Tracy set
up for next week!
- Hmm, great!
- Great!
You know, I am so glad
you didn't let that huge
embarrassing debacle
bring you down.
I mean, losing a man and
your job in front of everyone,
whew, that is tough.
But, so glad to see ya
back on your two feet.
Tracy'll call ya next week?
- Great Shelby.
- It was so nice meeting you.
- Oh, wonderful.
Nice to meet you too.
- Thank you.
I'm gon' let you
guys keep lunchin'.
All right, come on honey.
- Take care, Shelby!
- What's up, superstar?
- Austin, what are
you doing here?
- Actually I wanna get
to that in a second,
but I have a question for you.
Uh, you and Jillian,
y'all close?
- Yeah, she's been my
best friend since high school.
Why are you asking about her?
- No reason.
Van gon' be late,
so here's some cards for support.
- What's this?
- Just some bullet points
that I think you should mention.
- Oh, I already have my bullets.
- And here are a few more.
You haven't read
em, check it out.
- Boy, I'm not talkin' about
your weekly countdown show!
It's not even on TV.
- It's a village.
I'm supposed to support you,
you gotta support me back!
- No, Austin.
I already have enough
to think about.
- Tia, you wouldn't even
be here if it wasn't for me.
Man, I'm...
- What?
- Look,
when you was wilin' out in the streets,
I was gettin' a smoothie.
I bumped the footage to Van.
He thought it was funny,
so we broke the story.
It started to blow
up on social media,
he offers you a job,
instant ratings.
You got me to thank
for your success!
Remember that.
- You ready to do this?
Our next guest at Wake
Up DC is no stranger to us.
In fact, she used to
host this morning show.
Please welcome Tia Logan.
- And thank you for
having me, Shelby.
I'm happy to be here.
- Oh, it's
great to have you here.
I mean, ya look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Looks like life
has been treating you well.
- It has, it has.
I never thought I would
be on this side of
the morning show, but here I am.
- Yes, yes.
Ya know, so let's go back.
A few months ago, you
broke the internet
with a video that surfaced.
In fact, we have it.
- The wedding is off!
- It's not what you think.
- See Malcolm,
you need to handle all this.
- Wait, baby wait.
- Bitch, what?!
- So Tia, we all
would like to know,
are you still that angry woman?
- No Shelby, actually, I'm not.
I look at that situation
as a blessing in disguise.
Had that not happened, I
wouldn't have discovered
this beautiful career
which I love so much.
- And before we talk about that,
we love to do
where are they now?
So, we reached out to your ex
so we can get an update
on his total annihilation.
Please, please, let's
give a warm welcome
to Malcolm Wright.
- What?
- Malcolm, welcome.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you for having me.
- Oh, thank you for coming.
So, Malcolm, tell us,
how have you been?
- Oh well Shelby,
if you had asked me that a few weeks ago,
I would've said terrible.
But, now that I have
my other half back,
things couldn't be better.
- Oh, how sweet!
So, are you telling us that
you two are back together?
- No.
- Well actually,
Tia, I love you
and I wanna spend the rest
of my life making you happy.
Will you please marry me?
- Well?
- I don't wanna do this here.
- Believe me when I say
that I know that there is
no one I'd rather
spend my forever with.
We're gonna have a
great life together.
- Girl, are you gon' sit
here and let that man
pour his heart out in
front of 3.5 million people?
- 3.5?
- Yes, it's gone up
since I've become host.
- Yes, yes I will
marry you Malcolm.
- That is beautiful!
Look,
you have heard it here first on Wake Up DC.
#AngryBlackWoman is
now #HappyBrideToBe.
Again!
We'll be right back.
- What's up with you and
what was up with Malcolm?
What was that?
- I didn't plan that.
I didn't plan that.
When were you gonna tell me?
- Tell you what?
- You used me!
Austin shot the video
and you broke the story.
Oh, I respect your art.
You the best of both worlds.
It's all bullshit!
- That was the truth!
But I still got a job, Tia!
I still got a job!
- You know what,
you're worse than Malcolm
but at least Malcolm
knows how to stand up
and be a real man.
- OK yes, OK yes,
I should've told you, all right?
I should've told you but I
wanted you here because
I know you still got so
much more to offer, OK?
- You know what, it's funny.
I'm quitting for the
exact same reason.
I thought you were
one of the good guys.
- Man!
- You did what?
- I needed to forgive him.
- Then say we're
cool, don't say I do!
- It's hard out here, Jillian.
- Yeah, sure it is.
- It is hard!
And Malcolm wants to be with me.
No, he's not perfect but
at least he's trying.
- You know who you sound
like right about now?
- So what?
There's nothing wrong with
wanting to have a
good life, Jillian.
The big picture is
what's important.
- But Tia, do you
love him, honestly?
- Yes!
- Well, there you have it.
I guess settling
is the new love.
- At least I'm willing
to put myself out here
even after I've been hurt.
Yeah, you haven't
given a man a real shot
since Brooks left.
Yeah you claim to be this,
"Oh I'm a free spirited person,"
but it's all a facade.
You never take any
chances anymore,
not with anything!
- Well at least I don't
keep making bad decisions!
- It takes courage to
keep getting back out here.
What are you doing?
- I'm not runnin' around
here making people think
I got it all.
- Yeah,
because you went around here sleeping with
every Tom, Dick, and Butch.
- Get out.
Get out!
- You know what?
Can't tell you anything.
- And take your stanky
ass flowers with you!
- This advice thing
is a lot of pressure.
I met this woman today
who took her husband back
simply because I took you back.
- That's a good thing, right?
- I guess.
But what if she shouldn't have?
She's lookin' at my life
like it's perfect but...
- It is perfect
especially now that you
over that angry black thing.
I gotta say, that did
not go over too well
with the overheads at the firm.
My father was certainly
not impressed.
- What are you lookin' at?
- Give me back my phone.
- What's the problem?
I can't look through your phone?
- You can look through my phone,
but you should ask instead
of just grabbing it from me.
I know you don't trust me.
- Should I?
- I don't have anything to hide.
I promise.
Go ahead, look.
- Fine then, I will.
- Uh huh, told you.
I'm doin' right by you, baby.
- TJ called me about
coming back to the station
to be a field reporter.
- You should.
- But I don't know if I
wanna go back to that old,
stuffy job.
- That's the beauty
of being married to me.
You can go back to work or
you can just be Mrs. Wright.
- Logan-Wright.
- I'll just call you mine.
Now seriously, I gotta
get back to work.
- Oh, I signed us up for
Paint and Sip tomorrow.
- I'm sorry about
the paint thing.
- It wasn't a thing.
It was supposed to be a date.
- I should pick the
dates from now on.
- It's not always going to be about you,
Malcolm.
- Look, compromises
are hard for me.
- Marriage is one
big compromise.
- I know.
I know.
So please be patient with me.
I'm a work in progress.
You know what?
Why don't we just go down
to the courthouse this Friday.
I mean, let's just
go ahead and do it.
I don't want to wait and besides,
I don't have time
to plan anything big.
- You didn't really
plan the last one.
- Tia.
All I care about
is marrying you.
- OK.
But since the
reception is paid for,
can we still do the
party next month?
- Sure, whatever my baby wants.
- Don't do that.
Let it happen naturally.
Do not put yourself out there.
Once you do that, you
can't go back and yo,
once they break up with
you, they gon' act like,
oh they had the upper
hand the whole entire time
and it's not the case.
Damn man.
- You good bro?
You the angry black woman now?
- Oh no, I'm good.
I'm just sayin', you
know what I'm sayin',
just trying to help.
- OK.
- I say be honest.
Test the waters.
Give him signals to let
him know you're interested
and see how he responds.
If you get nothing, back up.
- I'll tell you.
I'll show you a picture.
Don't button it
up, I like it open.
- You like it open?
- Yes.
- I like it closed.
- Hey Van.
- Hey, what up, dawg?
- How y'all doin'?
- No just...
- Open it again.
- That's definitely in.
You are hilarious.
- That's cute.
- May I set a
dressing room for you?
- Sure.
Uh, let's see.
This one too.
Thank you.
- Get in here.
Grayson called me
about the book.
- I know, I guess it
wasn't meant to be.
- What?!
No, I'm not gon'
let you give up!
I thought it was a
really good idea.
- Hm, you cookin'?
- No, you know I don't cook.
- Smells like you
burnin' something.
- I don't cook.
I need to get the
elephant out the room.
I'm sleeping with Austin.
- I'm still marrying Malcolm.
Wait, that's the elephant?!
- I know.
I just gotta get it
off my conscience.
Listen,
I know he's young but what he lacks in age,
he makes up for in bed.
You hear me?
He's so young, he's so vibrant.
He just stimulate my whole body.
He just do somethin' to
me like you see it right now?
It's happening, you know?
- Oh God, the last thing
I need is the image
of you and Austin.
- Shut up.
You talk to Van?
OK, he talked to Ms.
Rashild about what happened
on the morning show.
She made a call.
Once again, Shelby
is field anchor.
So it's bye bye DC!
- What?
- Yes, so I told you
that woman was powerful!
- Oh my God!
- I couldn't stand her anyway!
- Oh my gosh, I hated her.
- They needed to just fire her.
I don't know why they
holdin' onto her.
- I know, let her go!
- They might as well
just take you back.
- I'm here.
- I'm sayin'!
- Right!
That's why you my best friend.
- I know.
We should take a girl's
trip this weekend.
What?
- I'm getting married Friday.
Hey, this is Tia.
I'm unavailable right now.
Please leave a message.
- Hey Tia, it's Van.
I sent a text the other day.
I thought I'd just
leave a message.
I um...
I need to talk to you
about your key card.
You still have it.
- It might've cost me
a bag, but I did it
and I got my girl back.
Now what?
Can't keep a winner down, baby.
- Go ahead babe, I need
to find a parking spot.
- You're coming in, aren't you?
- If I find a
parking space, maybe.
If not, it's up to the universe.
Go on now!
- Hurry up!
- Good luck.
- Oh there's my
baby right there.
- Uh, how you doin'?
- Good!
- Let me see this.
Come on, let's see this.
Let's take this right here.
Look at that!
Hey baby, come on.
Why don't you tell the world
how much you love me, hmm?
All right OK, look,
tell the people,
you know, how glad you're happy
to have your man back.
Yeah.
- Oh, I can't marry you.
- Come on, stop trippin' babe.
Tell the people.
- Hey world.
You wanna know how much
I love Malcolm Wright?
Not as much as I love myself.
I can't marry you, Malcolm.
- What?
- This isn't real but one day,
I hope that we both
can find someone
who can appreciate
and love us for
who we truly are.
- Dude, are you still live?
- Oh, I was just
about to walk over.
- Relax, I'm not
getting married.
- What?
What did he do?
- Calm down, calm down.
He didn't do anything.
Malcolm is who he is
and I was silly enough
to believe that that was enough
and for somebody, it will be.
But I just realized that I need
and deserve so much more.
- And what made you
realize that, T?
T, this face!
- I know.
- Oh, you know what,
you know I'm here if you need me,
if you need a place to stay,
you know I got you.
- I'm getting my own place.
- Say that again.
- You know what you be doin'!
- OK girl, you don't
have to be so happy!
- You don't understand,
you was takin' up my space.
My goodness!
- You know what?
I think it's time for
me to get reacquainted
with the real me.
- You know what?
I like the real you.
Free girl. - Yeah!
- She be a little bitter sometimes,
but she all right.
- Ah, the past is the past.
Oh girl, listen!
Coming!
I said I'm coming!
Damn, I just.
I said I'm comin'!
Just hold on, just...
- I need to see your book.
- What book?
- The one I'm publishing.
- Oh my gosh, ah!
- Tia, Tia!
You know I don't like
all that mushy stuff.
Give me a high
five or something.
Look, I know you said I
don't take chances anymore.
So, if I'm gon' step out there,
why not take a bet on
somebody I believe in?
- Oh my God.
I've already started
collecting the stories.
Wait, hoo, hoo, hoo.
- Tia, what are you doin'?
- Here.
Girl, all kinda stories.
Races, religions, everything.
This is gonna be so dope.
- And since it's
already written,
it's just a matter of editing.
And I know tons of editors.
Might take a few weeks.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's my best friend,
that's my best friend,
friend, friend,
aye, get it friend!
Aye, that's my friend!
Hey!
Oh, oh, you know
what we should do?
We should plan a
huge release party
and announce the book
and your publishing.
- I like that.
You know what?
I'm gon' start
lookin' for venues.
- No need!
I know the perfect place.
- Hey, hey!
- Yes, lookin' like
a cherry popsicle.
Come on in.
Hey love.
Hi!
- Hi, I'm with WBX News.
- Yeah.
- Your face looks so familiar.
- Oh nope, I don't know you.
You look good.
- What do you mean
you don't know me?
- Purple little shirt.
- You know, I need
to get in there.
- Oh you don't, 'cause sir,
she's not allowed to come in.
You have a good day,
Betty Bo Peep, bye!
- It's my assignment.
I'm with WBX News.
What is her name?
- You kissed him!
- What, no I didn't.
- I saw you!
- No, you're seeing things.
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
- I'm not seeing
anything but that kiss.
- Tia, don't you
have something to do?
- I am so excited about tonight
and the release of my new book!
I'm even more excited
to be doing this project
with my best friend,
Jillian James.
Proud of us.
In my journey over the last year
being the angry black woman,
I realized that most of
the women I came across
had the same thing in common.
Loneliness.
Most times, it's the root of our anger,
our jealousy.
And for me, I desired
to be accepted.
Loneliness breaks the
spirit and no one can soar
with a broken spirit.
But, after receiving
several thousand emails
from women all
across the country,
I realized that we never
need to feel lonely.
Why?
Because we're all dealing
with the same concerns,
the same issues, the
same insecurities.
We just need to
connect to each other.
And I hope that my new
book can bridge that gap.
The Joy Of Losing It
All is a compilation of
100 stories from women
who lost or walked away from
everything and in the process,
found themselves.
These are uplifting stories,
heartfelt stories
about women who
rose from the ashes,
dusted themselves off,
and decided to soar.
Can the authors who are
in the house tonight
come and join me up here?
Just right here, yeah.
Thank you.
Gloria lost her son and
the foundation in his honor
has fed thousands of kids.
Keisha escaped an
abusive marriage
and she mentors girl
all around the world.
Listen hey, I can keep going.
But what I wanna do right now
is read to you just one
of the amazing stories
so you can see what I'm saying.
I'm in my 30's and I'm
a pretty powerful person
when it comes to my career.
I'm driven by work.
It has been the only
thing that is motivating me
over the years.
So much so that I related my personal value
to my career success.
Eventually, my brand
became my career.
I was fine with that until I
hurt someone I cared about,
which made me reevaluate
what was important.
Success doesn't matter if
you lose yourself in the process.
Maybe that's why it's
lonely at the top.
But after losing this person,
I realized that I don't wanna
be at the top by myself.
I found someone to walk this
journey with and I'm hoping
I can get a second
chance to show...
that I am really one
of the good guys.
- I'm sorry, Tia.
Let me start over.
- Wow, that's one woman
who won't be angry
or lonely for a long time!
- So um, I've been thinking.
I really miss being on the show.
Think I can come back?
- No.
We ain't gonna have no time
to be on The Gossip Room
when we're busy prepping
your own show every day.
- My own show?
- I mean, that is, if
that's still your dream
and everything. - Yes.
- Is it still your dream? - Mmhm, mmhm.
- Mmhm.
- Mmhm!
- Your dream is my dream, OK?
OK.
- Hi, hi, hi!
Hi! - Hi!
May I help you?
- Yes, yes.
I'm Shelby Steele and I'm with WBX News,
right?
And I'm supposed to be
in there like right now,
but some woman,
she kicked me out.
He knows who I'm talkin' about.
Could you, I don't even know
who she is. - We don't like the words
kicked out.
Let's just say you were
selectively dismissed.
- Select... wait.
OK, what just happened?
'Scuse me, uh, lady?
Uh, lady in red.
Get your girl.
OK, y'all workin' together.
OK, white people involved now,
OK it's gotten real.
All right, I'm out
here on the red carpet.
Media pass.
Whatever happened
to black magic, huh?
- Hello ladies!
Are you ready to excel?
- Yeah!
- I love this energy!
Nice!
Woo! All right!
I am Tia Logan, the
angry black woman,
and I, you saw the show right?
You saw the show, yes.
I'm the angry black woman
and I am here to help you
release, right? - Yeah, yes.
- Yes, right?
I think the best way
to get this started
is just to dig in with
your questions, right?
So uh, let's just talk.
- I'm going to start right in.
Do you think it's unhealthy to
go through your man's phone?
- Me too.
I would like to ask that.
- You would say yes.
I'm sick as hell.
- Oh my goodness, ladies.
I mean, who hasn't
done that, right?
Right, come on,
let's just be real with each other
here tonight, right?
I can admit,
I have done my fair share of snooping,
but I found that it just
made me more anxious
even when I found nothing.
But on the other hand,
had I gone through Malcolm's phone,
maybe I would've caught
the lyin' bastard!
Right?
You know what I'm sayin'?
Right, I say go
through his phone!
Give me some, give me some!
You gotta do what
you gotta do, right?
Just don't get caught.
- You got it.
- Yeah.
- Were all three
of you in on this?
- No, this was all my idea.
- We should go dance.
Let's go dance. - I don't dance.
I don't dance!
Oh, you tryin' to dance, dance.
- Let's dance.
- Hey y'all, we're gon' be back.
- We're not comin' back.
- We not comin' back.
Y'all do y'all thing.
- Well I also may not
dance but you know
I bust a move baby.
- Oh really?
- Yeah really.
- Oh, let me see what
you talkin' bout.
Whoa, like that? - You see what I'm sayin'?
Like that.
- But you did it,
but you did it!